You're reading a magazine. You come
across a full-page nude photo of a girl.
Is this testing whether I'm a
replicant or a lesbian, Mr. Deckard?
Just answer the questions, please.
You show it to your husband. He likes it
so much he hangs it on your bedroom wall.
I wouldn't let him.
Why not?
I should be in there for him.
One more question.
You're watching a stage play.
A banquet is in progress.
The guests are enjoying
an appetizer of raw oysters.
The entree consists of boiled dog.
Would you step out for
a few moments, Rachel?
Thank you.
She's a replicant, isn't she?
I'm impressed.
How many questions does
it usually take to spot one?
I don't get it, Tyrell.
How many questions?
Twenty, thirty, cross-referenced.
It took more than a
hundred for Rachel, didn't it?
She doesn't know.
She's beginning to suspect, I think.
Suspect? How can it not know what it is?
Commerce is our goal here at Tyrell.
More human than human is our motto.
Rachel is an experiment.
Nothing more.
We began to recognize in
them a strange obsession.
After all, they are emotionally
inexperienced with only a few years
in which to store up the experiences
which you and I take for granted.
If we gift them for the past,
we create a cushion or pillow
for their emotions and consequently
we can control them better.
Memories.
You're talking about memories.