My partner tells me that your crew switched
to a P2P cook because of our success.
You dye your meth with food
coloring to make it look like mine.
You already ape my product at every turn.
But now, you have the
opportunity to sell it yourself.
I need you to listen to me.
We're not going to give up this deal to be
your errand boys, do you understand me?
For what?
To watch a bunch of
junkies get a better high?
A better high means customers pay more.
A higher purity means a greater yield.
That's $130 million of profit that isn't
being pissed away by some substandard cook.
Now, you listen to me.
You've got the greatest
meth cook in America.
No, the two greatest meth
cooks in America right here.
And with our skills, you'll earn more from
that 35% than you ever would on your own.
Yeah.
That's what you say.
Just wondering why we're so lucky.
Why cut us in?
Mike is retiring from our
crew, so his share of the
partnership is available
if you can handle his end.
Distribution.
And if you give him $5 million of
the $15 million that you brought
today, just think of it as a
finder's fee for bringing us together.
We have 40 pounds of product ready to ship.
Ready to go.
Are you ready?
Who the hell are you?
You know.
You all know exactly who I am.
Say my name.
Do what?
I don't have a damn
clue who the hell you are.
Yeah, you do.
I'm the cook.
I'm the man who killed Gus Fring.
Bullshit.
Cartel got Fring.
You sure?
That's right.
Now, say my name.
Heisenberg.
You're goddamn right.