Jimmy, please say something.
James?
What?
Who are you?
Mom, I thought you told me never to
talk to strangers.
Like I said before, Jimmy, please be nice
to your new stepfather.
Okay, rich guy, I love it that you're
twice as old as my grandfather and you're
fat and bald.
That's enough!
I've had it with you, you little brat!
You've upset your mother.
I've got half a mind to beat you.
Half a mind is right.
Suddenly he realizes.
I can't believe you, you little monster.
We'll deal with you when we get back
from our honeymoon.
Next year.
Here we are, boy.
Bullworth Academy.
Have fun, Jimmy.
I'll think of you from our cruise ship.
Whatever.
Mom, why'd you marry that phony?
What is wrong with you?
I can't believe this.