Is there something
troubling you, Quasimodo?
Oh, no!
Oh, but there is.
I know there is.
I think you're hiding something.
Oh, no, Master.
There's no... You're
not eating, boy.
Very good.
Thank you.
Seeds.
What's different in here?
Nothing, sir.
Isn't this one new?
It's awfully good.
Looks very much like the gypsy girl.
I know.
You helped her escape.
But I... Now all Paris is
burning because of you.
She was kind to me, Master.
You idiots!
That wasn't kindness.
It was cunning.
She's a gypsy.
Gypsies are not capable of real love.
Think, boy.
Think of your mother.
But what chance could
a poor, misshapen child
like you have against
her heathen treachery?
Well, never you mind, Quasimodo.
She'll be out of our lives soon enough.
I will free you from her evil spell.
She will torment you no longer.
What do you mean?
I know where her hideout is.
And tomorrow at dawn,
I attack with a thousand men.