In the Age of Ancients, the world
was unformed, shrouded by fog.
A land of grey crags, arch-trees,
and everlasting dragons.
But then there was fire,
and to his fire came disparity.
Heat and cold, life and death,
and of course, light and dark.
Then, from the dark, they came, and
found the souls of lords within the flame.
Nito, the first of the dead.
The witch of Izalith, and
her daughters of Chaos.
Gwyn, the lord of sunlight,
and his faithful knights.
And the furtive pygmy, so easily forgotten.
With the strength of lords,
they challenged the dragons.
Gwyn's mighty gods
peeled apart their stone-skills.
The witches weaved great fire-stores.
Nito unleashed a piasma
of death and disease.
And Seath, the scaleless betrayed his
own, and the dragons were no more.
Thus began the Age of Fire.
But soon the flames will
fade, and only dark will remain.
Even now there are only embers, and man
sees not light, but only endless lights.
And amongst the living are seen,
carriers of the accursed darksign.