I try to envision the events that take
place as individual elements.
I can then make a note of each one,
but I gain a better understanding when I
combine all of these again as a whole,
which is why I have very bad handwriting.
Any other questions?
Oh, oh!
Can you tell me if there's
something that you're not
good at, or maybe something
that you're scared of?
Something I'm scared of?
What?
Yeah, right.
Elle's not scared of anything.
Well, I suppose.
Monsters.
Me too.
I am too.
Dummy, Elle's not the same as you.
There are many types of monsters in this
world.
Monsters who will not show themselves and
who cause trouble.
Monsters who abduct children.
Monsters who devour dreams.
Monsters who suck blood.
And monsters who always tell lies.
Lying monsters are a real nuisance.
They are much more cunning than other
monsters.
A little pause...