Our appointment to FEMA should be
finalized within the week.
I've already discussed the matter with the
Senate.
I take it he was agreeable?
He didn't really have a choice.
Has he been infected?
Oh, yes.
Most certainly.
When I mentioned that we could put him on
the priority list for the Ambrosia
vaccine, he was so willing it was almost
pathetic.
This play, the rioting,
is intensifying to the
point where we may
not be able to contain it.
Why contain it?
Let it spill over to the schools and
churches.
Let the bodies pile up in the streets.
In the end, they'll beg us to save them.
I've received reports of armed attacks on
shipments.
There's not enough vaccine to go around.
And the underclasses are starting to get
desperate.
Of course they're desperate.
They can smell their death.
And the sound they'll make rattling their
cage will serve as a warning to the rest.