War. War never changes.
The Romans waged war
to gather slaves and wealth.
Spain built an empire from
its lust for gold and territory.
Hitler shaped a battered Germany
into an economic superpower.
But war never changes.
In the 21st century, war was still waged
over the resources that could be acquired.
Only this time, the spoils of
war were also its weapons.
Petroleum and uranium.
For these resources, China would invade
Alaska, the U.S. would annex Canada,
and the European
Commonwealth would dissolve
into quarreling,
bickering nation-states
bent on controlling the last
remaining resources on Earth.
In 2077, the storm of
World War had come again.
In two brief hours, most of the
planet was reduced to cinders.
And from the ashes of nuclear devastation,
a new civilization would struggle to arise.
A few were able to reach the relative
safety of the large underground vaults.
Your family was part of that
group that entered Vault 13.
Imprisoned safely behind the large
vault door, under a mountain of stone,
a generation has lived without
knowledge of the outside world.
Life in the vault is about to change.