Hey, I'm out at a ravine.
What's this thing that spans across it?
That is how you get to my sector.
No kidding.
Well, let me hike over.
Well, it's locked up in mainly for
emergencies.
I've never actually used it.
Rangers use it from time to time,
but that's it.
Help!
Oh, God!
It's an emergency!
Oh, really?
Yeah, I got eyes on a tornado!
I gotta get out of here!
A tornado in the heart of the Rockies?
Yes!
Holy moly, I need to call this in!
Tom, Two Forks sees a tornado.
He says he needs an evac into my sector.
It's a meteorological impossibility?
There haven't been
tornadoes in the Greater
Yellowstone Region in
a hundred million years?!
You´re going to need him to stay and take a detailed personal account even if it means giving his life?
Okay, I´II tell him!
Sorry, Hank.
No dice.
Man...