Hey, Smoke!
Hey, CJ, I was wondering
when you would show up.
How'd you know it was me?
Knew it was my old dog, CJ. Knew
you was coming and I don't give a shit.
I'm here to take care of your
fat ass. Then I'm gonna take
care of your friends in the
police department. Where they at?
Man, fuck this shit.
Man, that's some good shit.
Man, you went tenpenny.
Man, fuck tenpenny and fuck his
Polish lapdog and fuck the police, man.
Oh, that's old
shit. Look at you.
You got the whole world.
I ain't got no regrets, man.
Smoke you hot.
I made it, CJ. I'm a success.
I can't be touched.
I don't give a fuck. Fuck the whole world.
What happened to you, man?
Man, what the fuck do you care?
Uh, I guess we better do this shit, then.