I sure wish I could
learn how to... box.
Well, uh, you see, I'd really like to
learn the art of boxing.
Huh?
Well, yeah, what I'm saying is,
I really wish I could become a boxer.
Oh, wow, boxing's hardly the thing for a
little guy.
Let me think now, okay?
I can point you to the biceps of iron
protein diet or something.
Why don't you just do that?
Well, uh, you see, that's not really what
I'm talking about.
Huh?
I'd like to be a professional boxer.
I want to train and become strong and
compete in real matches.
Boxing's no play thing.
What?
Where do you get off making a
spur-of-the-moment decision to become a boxer?
It's not a spur-of-the-moment decision.
I'm really serious.
I want to do it.
Well, think again!
This is not the kind of
world where some bully
little weakling like
you can easily survive!
I really have given it serious thought.
This really is a serious and
well-thought-out decision.
I want to be a boxer.
I want to be really strong.
I want to be a new person!
How does it... How does
it feel to be so strong?
How does it feel to be strong like you?
Who... How does it feel to be-