Guys, looks like we'll be approaching
the wormhole in about three hours.
Hey, Coop.
Can we stop the spinning?
Why?
Because we're close enough to see him now.
All right.
Thanks.
There, that's it. That's the wormhole.
You say it don't spread here, huh?
It's a sphere.
Of course it is what you
thought it would just be a hole.
No, it's just that all the
illustrations I've ever seen, eh?
Illustrations.
Let me show you how it works.
So they say you want
to go from here to there.
But it's too far, right?
Mm-hmm.
So a wormhole bends space like this.
So you can take a shortcut
through a higher dimension.
Okay.
Okay, so to show that, they've turned
three-dimensional space into two dimensions,
which turns a wormhole
into two dimensions, a circle.
What's a circle in three dimensions?
Sphere.
Exactly.
A spherical hole.
But who put it there?
Who do we have to thank?
Well, I'm not thanking anybody until
we get out of here in one piece, Rom.
A trick to this, Doyle?
No one knows.
How'd the others made it, right?
At least some of them.