Excuse me.
Oh, I'm sorry. I.
I. Oh, it's. Okay.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm kind of lost.
Lost?
Yeah.
I'm looking for Silent Hill.
Is this the right way?
Yeah.
It's hard to see with this fog,
but there's only the one road.
You can't miss it.
Thanks,
but yes.
I think you'd better stay away.
This.
This town.
There's something wrong with it.
It's kind of hard to explain, but.
Is it dangerous?
Maybe.
And it's not just a fog either.
Okay, I got it.
I'll be careful.
I'm not lying.
No, I believe you.
It's just.
I guess I really don't care
if it's dangerous or not.
I'm going to town either way.
But why?
I'm looking for someone.
Who is it?
Someone
very important to me.
I'd do anything
if I could be with her again.