Sorry that I failed to mention your exams.
I was busy dealing with some of Shido's
cronies.
Well, you are students, so it's only
fitting you're doing a study group.
You're gonna bring us some snacks now and
then, right?
You don't even have exams.
Pardon the intrusion.
Glad to see you all.
Don't mind me.
Make yourselves at home.
You're too kind.
We'll take you up on that offer.
Why did you bring me here?
My school's exams are already over.
Come on, don't be so cold.
You're saying it's fine if I fail?
Nothing wrong with that.
Won't the results be the same whether you
study or not?
Now, now, you guys.
Just think of it as helping me out.
I don't know about this.
I'm just going to focus on sections that
may likely be on the test.
You're way too short on time.
Making a gamble, huh?
If she's wrong, we die.
Aw, I don't wanna die.
Um, is it really that bad?
This is every day for them.
This affects you, too.