You think you could
deceive me, Barrel Rider?
You have come from Lake Town.
This is some sordid
skee-mat between these filthy
dwarfs and those miserable
top-trading lake-men.
Those sniveling cowards with
their long bows and black arrows.
Perhaps it is time I paid them a visit.
Oh, no.
This isn't their fault!
Wait!
You cannot go to Lake Town!
You care about them, do you?
Good.
Then you can watch them die.
Here!
You witless worm!
I am king under the mountain.
This is not your kingdom.
These are dwarf lands.
This is dwarf gold.
And we will have our revenge.
Revenge!
I will show you revenge!
Listen to me!
Do you not know what is coming?
What have we done?
I am fire!
I am...
Death!