Oh, no thanks.
I love life.
Huh?
But you just got dumped.
Well, yeah, and I'm sad.
But at the same time, I'm really happy
that something can make me feel that sad.
It's like... it makes me feel alive,
you know?
It makes me feel human.
The only way I can feel this sad now is if
I felt something really good before.
So I have to take the bad with the good.
So I guess what I'm feeling is like a
beautiful sadness.
I guess that sounds stupid.
Yeah.
Wow.
No.
No, Butters, that doesn't sound stupid at
all.
Thanks for offering to let me in your
clique, guys.
But to be honest, I'd rather be a crying
little pussy than a faggy goth kid.
We'll see you, Stan.
He's right.
I don't even know who I am anymore.
I like liking life a lot more than hating
it.
Screw you guys.
I'm going home.
Go ahead and...