Thanks for the ride.
Wait a minute.
We need to talk.
We can talk later.
We can talk now.
If you let me.
What do we have to talk about?
Why now?
Because we haven't talked at all for so
long.
Your Aunt May and I don't even know who
you are anymore.
You shirk your chores.
You have all those weird experiments in
your room.
You start fights at school.
I didn't start that fight.
I told you that.
You sure as hell finished.
What was I supposed to do?
Run away?
No.
You're not supposed to run away.
But... Pete, look.
You're changing.
I know.
I went through exactly the same thing at
your age.
No.
Not exactly.
Peter.
These are the years when
a man changes into the
man he's going to
become the rest of his life.
Just be careful who you change into.
This guy Flash Thompson.
He probably deserved what happened.
But just because you can beat him up...
He doesn't give me the right to.
Remember... With great power... Comes
great responsibility.
...comes great responsibility.
Are you afraid that I'm going to turn into
some kind of criminal?
Quit worrying about me, okay?
Something's different.
I'll figure it out.
Stop lecturing me, please.
I don't mean to lecture and I don't mean
to preach.
And I know I'm not your father.
Then stop pretending to be.
Right.
I'll pick you up here at 10.