The plans you refer to will soon be back
in our hands.
Any attack made by the rebels against this
station would be a useless gesture.
No matter what technical
data they've obtained, this
station is now the ultimate
power in the universe.
I suggest we use it.
Don't be too proud of this technological
terror you've constructed.
The ability to destroy a planet is
insignificant next to the power of the Force.
Don't try to frighten us with your
sorcerer's ways, Lord Vader.
Your sad devotion to
that ancient religion has
not helped you conjure
up the stolen data tapes.
Or given you clairvoyance enough to find
the rebels' hidden fortress.
I find your lack of faith disturbing.
Enough of this.
Vader, release him.
As you wish.