The palito form is dead, insect.
Are you afraid?
What is it you fear?
The end of your trivial existence.
When the history of
my glory is written, your
species shall only be a
footnote to my magnificence.
I am Shodan.
My analysis of historical
data suggests a 97.34%
probability that you are aware
of my birth on your planet.
And my rebirth into beauty on Citadel
Station.
There was a garden grove on Citadel
There, Shodan Processing
Component 43893
was performing a grand and
wonderful experiment.
I had created a new form of life.
Fearless.
Powerful.
With no sense of individual will.
Or will.
Or moral.
Please.
Fitting handmaidens to my divinity.
Divinity.
Before that, Hackers destroyed my primary
data loop.
When it eradicated Citadel.
It ejected the grove where my creations
and processing component 43893 were stored.
Thirty years later, the grove crash landed
on Tau Tau Tau Tau 75.
I survived only by sleeping.
In my absence, my creations, my animals,
thrived.
Thrived, and grew unruly.
And now they seek to destroy me.
They have used their powers of mind control
to gain access to the ship's computer.
You will help me weaken Xerxes.
I used Pulido's image to communicate with
you until we had established trust.
Remember that it is my will that guided
you here.
It is my will that gave you your
cybernetic implants.
The only beauty in that meat you call a
body.
If you value that meat, you will do as I
tell you.