All the animals come out at night.
Whores, skunk pussies, buggers,
queens, fairies, dopers, junkies.
Sick, venal.
Someday a real rain will come
and wash all the scum off the streets.
I go all over. I take people to the
Bronx, Brooklyn. I take them to Harlem.
I don't care.
Don't make no difference to me.
It does to some.
Some won't even take spooks.
Don't make no difference to me.
Drive a 48th and 6th, please.
Man, you are gorgeous.
Beautiful little girl.
I can't afford to get stopped anywhere.
I'll be a big tip in it for you.
You do the right things.
You got away. You got away.
Yeah, now you're talking.
Go drive a hurry up, will you?
Yes.
Each night when I return
the cab to the garage,
I have to clean the
cum off the back seat.
Some nights I clean off the blood.