You understand?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's cool.
Just for a couple of weeks.
I understand.
Maybe a little longer.
Yeah, whatever.
Whatever.
Look, I'll call you next week and we'll
iron out the details.
Okay?
Yeah, yeah.
It was great seeing you, son.
You too.
Lou.
Yeah, um...
I'm sorry, Will.
You know what?
Actually, this works out better for me.
You know, the Slimmies of Summer come to
class wearing next to nothing.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, it's alright to be angry.
Hey, why should I be mad?
I'm saying, at least he said goodbye this
time.
I just wish I hadn't wasted my money
buying this stupid present.
I'm sorry.
You know, if there was something
that I could do... Hey, you know what?
You ain't got to do nothing, Uncle Phil.
You know, ain't like I'm still five years
old, you know?
Ain't like I'm going to
be sitting up every night
asking my mom, when's
daddy coming home, you know?
Who needs him?
Hey, he wasn't there to
teach me how to shoot
my first basket, but
I learned, didn't I?
Hey, I got pretty damn good attitude,
didn't I, Uncle Phil?
Got through my first day without him,
right?
I learned how to drive.
I learned how to shave.
I learned how to fight without him.
I had 14 great birthdays without him.
He never even sent me a damn card.
To hell with him!
I ain't need him then, and I don't need
him now.
Well, well... Now, you
know what, Uncle Phil?
I'm going to get through college without
him.
I'm going to get a great job without him.
I'm going to marry me
a beautiful honey, and
I'm going to have me
a whole bunch of kids.
I'm going to be a better father than he
ever was.
And I sure as hell don't need
him for that, because ain't a
damn thing he could ever teach
me about how to love my kids!
How come he don't want me, man?