Excuse me.
Hey, hey, you got a visitor.
Shut up, you.
And what you want?
My name's John Marston.
You wanted to speak to me.
I did?
Apparently so.
Why?
I guess because we're both
in the business of the law.
You that fella from the train company?
No, I'm from Fort Mercer.
Fort Mercer?
You them one of them Williamson boys.
Calm down.
Go on, shoot them, mister. Shoot them.
Come on, what?
You getting cute with me, boy?
What's going on here?
I got me one of them Williamson boys.
I got me one of them idiots
who give marshals a bad name.
Jonah, put your gun down.
You must be the man from Blackwater.
Yes, sir.
Listen, that dog ain't too bright.
But he seems loyal.
Jonah, get out of here for a minute.
Yes, sir, Mr. Johnson, sir.
And you.
Oh, I done seen enough of
your hide around here, friend.
I think there's some school children
down the way you can go and frighten.
Oh, hardy fucking hard.
Dickhead.
What are you doing here, Mr. Marston?
Apart from frightening my deputies.
I'm here to capture
or kill Bill Williamson.
Okay.
Can you help me?
He's outside my jurisdiction.
He's in the next county.
Of course, Bill Williamson
and his boys have
tended to keep themselves
away from my town.
So you're happy to have him out there?
I ain't happy, but I also ain't suicidal.
My job is to keep this town safe, not
clean up to all of these three counties.
It's hard enough around here.
You know, I hear you speak, and
suddenly I'm reminded of how some of
the people I respected most in
my life had a problem with authority.
What's wrong with you?
Well, I'm sure you and your
fine friends have enjoyed
spending your time running
around pursuing noble causes.
My cause is to keep
this town from turning
into a living hell for
the folks who live here.
Whole world has problems, mister.
And I'm here doing what I can.
Why? What's happening?
Right now?
I got the railway, the people
who pay my salary, trying to get
me to turn a blind eye to them
burning down settlements up there.
I got a bunch of cattle rustlers out
near Box Canyon need shutting down.
I'm forgetting the gang that keeps murdering
homesteaders out in the backcountry.
And I got a bunch of
hoods over in the saloon,
drunk, threatening to
shoot up the whole town.
That's all I got today.
But it's early yet.
Give me a couple more days.
There'll be more.
All right.
Tell you what.
Let's go deal with them
hoods in the saloon.
Then we'll discuss Williamson.
Okay, boy.
You're persistent, little cuss, ain't you?
Only when things matter.