Hey, Rick, I have to make a project for
the science fair this weekend.
You think you could help me out?
Whatever.
Well, I mean, traditionally, science fairs
are a father-son thing.
Well, scientifically, traditions are an
idiot thing.
Morty, I think it would be fun for you to
work on a science project with your dad.
Yeah, Dad, why don't we do it together?
Yes!
You backed the right horse on this one,
son.
We'll get out the
crayons, brew some coffee,
and knock this thing
out in two or three days.
What is my purpose?
Pass the butter.
Thank you.
Dad, I need a ride to work.
Maybe Rick can give you a ride.
I'm helping Morty with science.
I'm busy.
Doing what?
Uh, anything else?
What is my purpose?
You pass butter.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, welcome to the club, pal.