The moment in the garden, the
idea of allowing your own crucifixion.
But you're not a Christian,
so what do you believe?
I believe that people shouldn't
talk about this type of shit at work.
Hold on, hold on.
Three months we've been
together, I get nothing from you.
And today, what we're into
now, do me a courtesy, okay?
I'm not trying to convert you.
Look, I'd consider
myself a realist, all right?
But in philosophical terms,
I'm what's called a pessimist.
Um, okay, what's that mean?
It means I'm bad at parties.
Let me tell you, you ain't
great outside of parties either.
I think human consciousness
is a tragic misstep in evolution.
We became too self-aware.
Nature created an aspect
of nature separate from itself.
We are creatures that
should not exist by natural law.
Hmm, that sounds god-fucking-awful, Rush.
We are things that labor under
the illusion of having a self.
This accretion of sensory
experience and feeling.
Programmed with total assurance
that we are each somebody.
When in fact, everybody's nobody.
I wouldn't go around
spouting that shit out with you.
People around here don't think that way.
I don't think that way.
I think the honorable thing for our
species to do is deny our programming.
Stop reproducing.
Walk hand in hand into extinction.
One last midnight, brothers and
sisters opting out of a raw deal.
So, what's the point of getting
out of bed in the morning?
I tell myself I bear witness.
The real answer is that it's
obviously my programming.
And I lack the constitution for suicide.
My luck, I picked today to get to know you.
Three months, I don't hear a
word from you and...
You asked.
Yeah.
And now I'm begging
you to shut the fuck up.
I've got a bad taste in my mouth out here.
Aluminum.
Ash.
I can smell the psychosphere.
I got an idea.
Let's make the car a place of
silent reflection from now on.
Okay?
What should I bring for dinner?
A bottle of wine would be nice, I guess.
I don't drink.
Oh, no, of course not, Russ.
Listen, when you're at my house,
I want you to chill the fuck out.
Don't even mention any of
that bullshit you just said to me.
Of course not, Marty.
I'm not some kind of maniac, right?
Well, for fuck's sake.